(忆往昔)
你们什么人  警察吗
Who are you, cops?
你们是《X档案》
You guys are "X-files."
嗯  行啊  可以这么说
Sure. Yeah. You could say that.
该隐仍然有血印  对吗
Cain still has the mark, right?
多年来  他一直带着它
So he's lived with it for years.
血印很强大
The mark is -- is strong.
也许你得与之斗争
Maybe you have to fight that.
迪恩  你以为恶鬼是怎么来的
Dean, how do you think angry spirits are born?
他们无法放手  无法向前看
They can't let go, and they can't move on.
就像受伤的动物
Like wounded animals.
迷失  痛苦不堪  便发脾气
Lost. In so much pain, they lash out.
为什么  他们为什么留在这里
Why? Why are they here?
他们有一部分  把他们留在了这里
Well, there's some part of them that's keeping them here.
有些鬼魂不肯放手
Some spirits hold on too tight.
迪恩  你已经一周没离开地堡了
Dean, you haven't left the bunker in a week.
怎么了
And?
你不能余生都
You can't just live the rest of your life
把自己关在这间屋子里
Locked up in this room.
我知道你担心血印的事
I know you're worried about the mark.
是啊  萨姆  没错
Yes, Sam. I am.
我希望血印消失吗
Do I wish the mark was gone?
当然希望  绝对想
Yes, of course. Absolutely, I do.
我们会想到办法的
We'll figure it out.
我们一向如此
We always do.
说得对
Damn right.
(如今)
(爱荷华州  斯宾塞)
你真的可以开车吗
You sure you're okay to drive?
可能不太好吧
Not really.
灌点油水下去就好了
But it's nothing a little grease can't fix.
-崔妮  找到最近的塔可镇  -正在搜寻
- Trini, find me the nearest Taco Town. - Searching...
我要点个墨西哥干酪卷饼和辣酱
Ooh, I'm gonna get a quesarito and a chi-chi melt.
50英尺后右转
Turn right in 50 feet.
比利  这才不是去塔可镇的路呢
Um, Billy, I don't think this is the way to Taco Town.
你怎么知道  这手机有3G呢
What do you know? Your phone's 3g.
崔妮从不犯错
Trini doesn't make mistakes.
继续前行0.3英里  然后左转
Continue for .3 miles, then turn left.
冷死了  把空调关了吧
It's freezing. Can you please turn off the air?
没开啊
It's not on.
(危险  桥梁禁行)
搞什么
What the hell?
还说崔妮不犯错呢
Trini doesn't make mistakes, huh?
崔妮  再找条路线
Trini, find a different route.
请前行
Proceed ahead.
去你的
Go screw yourself.
去你的吧
You go screw yourself.
珍妮特  下车
Janet, get out of the truck.
她怎么知道我叫什么
Um, how does she know my name?
珍妮特  叫你下车  马上
Janet, get out of the truck, now!
天呐
Oh, my god.
救命
Help!
不要  等等  停车
No, wait! Stop!
比利
Billy!
不要啊
No! No!
不要  救命
No! Help!
比利
Billy!
停下
Stop!
绝命终点就在正前方
Destination dead ahead.
[邪恶力量 第10季第13集]
搞什么
What in the world?
-可颂饼干  -可颂饼干
- A croissookie. - A croissookie?
对  可颂甜甜圈之后的新潮流
Mm-hmm. Yeah, they're the new cronuts.
怎么  半饼干  半...
Okay. So, what? Half cookie, half...
管他呢  好吃极了
Who gives a crap? They're freakin' awesome.
小卡怎么说
What did Cass say?
有好消息  有坏消息
Uh, good news, bad news.
坏消息  他喜欢上了江轮赌博
Bad news... he discovered riverboat gambling.
好消息是  他觉得他可能要找到该隐了
Good news... he thinks he might be closing in on Cain.
-他觉得可能啊  -嗯
- Thinks he might be. - Yeah.
密西西比以东  伊利诺伊州什么地方
Just east of the Mississippi somewhere in Illinois.
或许小卡能在林肯的故乡找到该隐
So, maybe Cass finds Cain in the Land of Lincoln.
然后呢
And then what?
然后我们让他说出怎么摆脱血印
And then we get him to tell us how to get rid of the mark.
你不觉得如果该隐知道怎么去除血印
Don't you think that if Cain knew how to remove the mark,
他几个世纪之前就会做了吗
he would have done it, like, centuries ago?
总得试试才确定
We won't know till we try.
萨姆  我感谢你这么努力  真的
Sammy, I appreciate the effort, man. I do.
但想找到这东西的解决办法
But trying to find a cure for this thing,
就像狗追尾巴
i-it's like a dog chasing its tail.
毫无希望  只会把人折腾一顿
There's no end in sight and you just end up dizzy.
迪恩  有志者
Dean, where there is a will...
必有案子
There is a case.
看看这个
Check this out.
爱荷华州少女称被魔鬼附身的卡车害死了司机
"Iowa teen claims possessed pickup kills driver."
我们去中西部看看怎么样
Let's say we take our own trek to, uh, the midwest.
抱歉我逼你离开了大学
Sorry I ever made you leave.
天呐  到处都是
God, they're everywhere.
哪位是珍妮特·诺维塞里克
Uh, which one of you is Janet Novoselic?
我是
I am.
格罗尔和柯宾探员
Agents Grohl and Cobain.
再见
Bye.
我跟警察都说九遍了
I already talked to the police like nine times.
-嗯  这只是后续调查  -嗯
- Yeah, no, this is, uh... it's, uh, just a follow-up. - Yeah.
我明天还有期末考试
I have finals tomorrow.
那我们尽快问完  我保证
Then we'll make it fast. I promise.
我跟警探说了
It's like I told the detective.
我喝醉了  但我没有看花眼
I was drunk, but I wasn't hallucinating.
那辆车有自己的心思
The truck had a mind of its own.
怎么说
How so?
冷气直冒
Like, the air went full blast
但空调根本没开
even though it wasn't on
电台一团糟  还有崔妮也是
and the radio went crazy, and so did Trini.
崔妮是
And Trini is...?
请原谅我搭档
You have to excuse my partner.
他对科技发展不怎么熟悉
When it comes to technology, he is a little behind.
他才学会用脸书呢
He just learned how to poke on facebook.
崔妮是我们用的导航软件
Uh, um, Trini is the nav app we were using.
就像会说话的地图
It... it's like a talking map.
你是70后  好吧
You're gen x. Right.
那么说  崔妮和车上的一切
Okay, so, Trini and everything else in the truck
都"克里斯汀"了
went all "Christine."
那是谁
Who's Christine?
70后的情怀
It's a gen x thing.
听我说
Look.
我不指望你们相信我
I don't expect you to believe me.
但我发誓  那车一心想杀了比利
But I swear that truck was hell-bent on killing Billy.
比利有敌人吗
Did Billy have any enemies?
有谁跟他有仇吗
Anybody who might have had a beef with him?
或许他哥哥乔伊吧  他们总打架
Maybe his brother Joey. They fought all the time.
真可悲
It's so sad.
他们没机会和好了
They never got to set it right.
因为比利死了
Because Billy died.
不
No.
乔伊死了  死在了阿富汗
Joey did. In Afghanistan.
你知道他埋在哪吗
Do you know where he's buried?
他没下葬  他尸体没回国
He's not. Poor guy never came home.
自制炸弹
I.E.D.
比利死的时候有没有戴着什么他哥哥的东西
Did Billy happen to have anything of his brother's on him when he died?
铭牌  帽子之类的
Uh, dog tags, a hat, something?
就那辆车
Just his pickup.
车是乔伊的
So, the truck belonged to Joey?
没错  他可引以为豪了
Yeah. It was his pride and joy.
他死后比利继承了车  算是种情怀吧
Billy got it when he died, and, you know, it's a thing.
嗯
Yeah.
失陪一下
Excuse me a sec.
什么情怀啊
So... so, what's a thing?
就是车的情怀啊
You know, the truck thing.
开死者的车  算是对他的致敬
You honor the deceased by driving their truck.
萨姆  这种事都有乡村歌曲啊
Sam, they wrote a whole country song about it.
去谷歌一下啊  学霸
Why don't you google it?
那么我们要找一辆
All right, so, we're looking for something
原来是卡车的破烂
that used to resemble a pickup truck.
好吧
All right.
找到了
Here we go.
嗯  海军陆战队
Yeah, marine.
这应该不是油
I'm guessing this ain't oil.
那是灵质
That is ectoplasm.
看这个
Look at this.
乔伊吗
Joey?
看来是的
Looks like it.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧  哥哥跟弟弟感情不好
All right, so, big brother didn't get along with little brother,
不爽他开他的宝贝车了
was pissed that he was driving his baby.
这我懂
I get it.
怎么
What are you saying?
如果你死了  我开你的宝贝  你就杀我吗
If you died and I drove your car, you'd kill me?
如果你吃东西把车弄臭了  或许吧
If you stunk her up with tacquitos, probably.
好了  动手吧
All right. Let's do this.
看上去像一池子草
Makes it looks like a-a pool in reseda.
我们艺术史期末考试居然就在明天了
I can't believe our art history final's tomorrow.
是啊
I know.
这学期简直一闪而过啊
This semester, like, totally flew by.
嗯  喝醉的时候时光飞逝啊
Yeah. Time flies when you're drunk.
要跟我一起去图书馆吗
Want to come to the library with me?
我还有好多要背呢
I still have so much to memorize.
我还以为看裸男的画作会很轻松呢
And I thought looking at pictures of naked guys was gonna be easy.
谢了  但我不用学习了
Thanks, but I don't really need to study for it.
我有过目不忘的本事  上帝保佑
I have a photographic memory. Blessed.
你不用学习
Um, you don't need to study for it
是因为你在跟助教上床
because you're screwing the T.A.
小婊砸
Slut.
(来自"艾尔莎公主8"的聊天请求)
(- 你是谁  - 一个朋友)
(- 有趣  干什么呢  朋友  - 没什么  撒谎精)
(什么啊  我怎么撒谎了)
(810)
(我知道哦  你会付出代价)
(删除对话)
天呐  天呐
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
我要不行了
I'm not gonna make it.
集中精神
Focus.
室友黛莉拉·马里安今早发现了她
Delilah Marian... the roommate found her this morning
她昨晚去图书馆自习了
after an all-nighter at the library.
勒毙吗
Strangulation?
那变态用了电脑的电源线
Sicko used the power cord from the computer.
嫌疑人
Suspects?
还没有
None yet.
奇怪的是  门是锁上的
The odd thing was the door was locked.
跟其他住这里的女生谈过了吗
Have you talked to any of the other girls who live here?
大部分因为放春假已经走了
Well, most of them have already left for spring break.
但室友帮了大忙
But the roommate was really helpful.
给了我们朱莉的密码
She gave us all of Julie's passwords.
如今想了解青少年
And nowadays, the only way to find out anything
唯一的办法就是通过社交网络
about teenagers is through social media.
相信我  我家有俩青少年呢
Trust me. I got two of them.
失陪了  探员们
Excuse me, agents.
嗯  好的
Oh, yeah. Sure.
复仇鬼魂吗
Revengeful spirit, much?
但这是乔伊  还是另有其人
Yeah, but is it Joey's or another ghost?
不知道
I don't know.
起初是附身了一辆卡车
So, first it possesses a... a truck,
然后又是台电脑吗
and then it possesses a computer?
都是跟机械技术有关的
Both machine-related kills.
怎么  你认为这是个
So, what? You think we're dealing with a
"机器里的鬼魂"
"Ghost in the machine"?
可能吧
Maybe.
但如果是同一个鬼魂
But if it is the same ghost, I mean,
他们一般把自己跟某个地方或东西绑在一起
they usually anchor themselves to a place or a thing.
这个鬼怎么能从一台机器跳到另一台机器上
How is this one jumping from one machine to the next?
多谢帮忙  黛莉拉
We really appreciate your help, Delilah.
我们知道你一定很难过
We know this can't possibly be easy.
朱莉会不会认识比利·巴斯
Did Julie, by chance, know a student named Billy Bass?
人人都认识比利
Everyone knew Billy.
他是Σθδ的主席
He was the president of sigma theta delta.
STD(性病)吗
Std?
对
Yeah.
是校园最大的兄弟会
It's the biggest frat on campus.
朱莉认识比利的哥哥  乔伊吗
Did, uh... did Julie know Billy's brother Joey,
那个当兵的
The... the soldier?
应该不认识
I don't think so.
我都不知道比利有哥哥
I didn't even know Billy had a brother.
她有敌人吗
Did she have any enemies?
有人会想伤害她吗
Any reason why someone might want to hurt her?
没有
No.
朱莉真的很受欢迎  人很好
Julie was really popular, super-sweet.
我无法想象有人会想伤害她
I can't imagine anyone wanting to hurt her.
你知道我们是联邦探员吧
You know we're federal agents, right?
跟我们撒谎是重罪
Lying to us is a big-time offense.
我没撒谎  探员
I'm not lying, agent.
实在没什么可说的
There's just... nothing else to tell.
好了
All right
这位女士的咖啡加奶
And a café au lait for the lady.
-我的...  -心脏病吗
- For me... - A heart attack?
这简直不真实
This is unreal.
瞧啊  意大利餐  中餐
Look at this. I got Italian. I got Chinese.
自助冻酸奶
Serve-yourself froyo.
大学比维加斯还棒
College is better than Vegas.
有什么发现
What do you got?
很不幸  没发现什么
Unfortunately, a... a lot of nada.
我看了朱莉的脸书  图片分享  推特
I hit up Julie's facebook, instagram, twitter,
即时聊天  阅后即焚  聊天器
InstaChat, SNAPCHAT, A.I.M.,
只有关于《极速风流》和《五十度灰》的帖子
nothing but posts on Rush and "Fifty Shades of Grey""
电影  不是书
The movie, not the book.
嗯  我一半没听懂
Yeah, I didn't get half of that.
无所谓
It doesn't matter.
我在搜查她的删除文件
Now I'm going through her deleted files.
这你也会
You can do that?
嗯
Yeah.
网上没什么东西真正能删除
I mean, nothing ever really gets deleted from the internet.
你知道的吧
You knew that, right?
当然
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
我看看  我可能有发现
Here we go. This might be something.
是一则被删除的昨晚的即时聊天记录
It's a... it's a deleted InstaChat from last night
就在死亡时间前后
right around time of death.
跟谁
With who?
艾尔莎公主8
With PrincessElsa8.
看
Look at this.
撒谎精
"Liar."
我知道哦  你会付出代价
"I know." "You'll pay."
这个艾尔莎公主不是什么好鸟啊
Well, This PrincessElsa's a bitch.
810是什么
What is 810?
-810  -嗯
- 810? - Yeah.
是...
Uh, it's a...
我不知道
I don't know.
或许是日期
Maybe it's a date.
或许是时间  或者区号
Maybe it's a time of day. Or an area code.
如果是区号  是密执根东南部
Uh, area code is for southeast Michigan.
哎呦
You know what?
有发现了
Here we go.
斯宾塞有三个地址包含了810
Uh, there are three address in spencer that have "810" in them.
我看看这东西能不能打包
I'll see if I can get this to go.
(唐斯大道810号)
嗯  好的
Yeah. You got it.
谢谢  佩特伦奇克警探  我们再联系
Thank you, Detective Petranzyk. We will keep in touch.
艾尔莎公主8不是一个疯狂的网络杀手
So, PrincessElsa8 is not some crazed cyber killer.
她是威斯康辛州内巴格蒙湖的一个三年级学生
She is a third grader from Lake Nebagamon, Wisconsin,
超迷《冰雪奇缘》
who is obsessed with "Frozen."
死者即时聊天的时候她睡得正熟
And she was fast asleep when the InstaChat occurred.
这么说是黑客干的
So, a hack job.
我也是这么想的
That's what I'm thinking.
打扰一下  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
能问一下你在做什么吗
May we, uh, ask what you're doing?
把枯萎的花扔掉  这也犯法吗
Um, throwing away dead flowers. Is that a crime?
不是  只是有点奇怪
Well, it's not a crime, just a little strange,
鉴于花还没枯
uh, seeing as how they aren't dead.
如果你觉得它们在嘲笑你  就不那么奇怪了
It's not so strange when it feels like they're taunting you.
九个月前我丈夫在这里死于车祸
My husband was killed in a car accident here nine months ago.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
节哀顺变
Our condolences.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们才刚结婚
We were newlyweds.
还没撑到第一个结婚纪念日
Never even made it to our first anniversary.
每次我从窗口往外望
And to have to be reminded of that
或者出门的时候  它们都会提醒我...
every time I look out my window or leave the house...
可以理解
Understandable.
抱歉  请问在你丈夫去世后
Forgive me, but did you notice anything...
你有没有注意到什么诡异的事
weird after your husband's death?
比如什么奇怪的异动或者...
Any strange disturbances or...?
我不明白你的意思
I'm not sure what you mean.
没事  算了
It's nothing. Never mind.
知道这些花是谁留下的吗
Any idea who's leaving the flowers?
一个十几岁的女孩
Some teenage girl.
我想她应该上大学了
I think she goes to the college
她总穿联谊会的衣服
'cause she's always in Greek letters.
你知道她的名字吗
Do you know her name?
不知道
No.
她留着一头长长的红发
Uh, she has long red hair.
还是我  格罗尔探员
This is agent Grohl again.
听着  我知道我叫你
Listen, I know I told you to call
方便时尽早打给我  但这话当我没说
at your earliest convenience, but scratch that.
马上打给我
Call A.S.A.P.
瞧瞧这个
Look at this.
安德鲁·西尔弗
Uh, Andrew Silver,
29岁斯宾塞高中教师
"29-year-old spencer high-school teacher
死于一场致命车祸
killed in fatal accident.
事故车辆起火
Uh, car burst into flames.
西尔弗的尸体被烧得面目全非
Silver's body was burned beyond recognition.
据信他在车辆撞击时已经身亡
And he is believed to have been killed upon impact"
(29岁斯宾塞高中教师死于致命车祸)
好吧
Okay.
这个叫安迪的怨鬼  他死在唐斯大道810号
So, Andy the angry ghost -- he dies at 810 Downs Drive.
他把"810"发到朱莉的电脑上来折磨她
and then he torments Julie with 810 on her computer.
他跟她有什么过节
So, what's his beef with her?
对  他跟比利又有什么关系
Yeah, and what's his connection to Billy?
上面写他被埋葬在哪里了吗
Does it say where he's buried?
他没有被埋葬  他被火化了
He wasn't. He was cremated.
没有尸骨
So, no bones,
而且据我们所知  他也没附在什么东西上
and he's not tethered to any object that we know of.
对  安德鲁是怎么找上被害人的
Yeah. How is Andrew haunting his victims?
你打算全吃了吗
Are you gonna eat all that?
对啊  你要来点吗
Yeah. You want some?
联调局的又打来了  三回了
The Feds called... like three times already.
凯尔  你听见我说的了吗
Kyle, are you listening to me?!
我觉得他们知道了
I think they know.
也许我们该去坦白一切
Maybe it's time we should come clean.
不可能
Uh, that's not gonna happen.
就因为我们闭口不言  你看都发生了什么
Look where keeping our mouths shut got us.
我觉得是报应
I think it's karma.
也许我们被诅咒了
Maybe we're being cursed or something.
我也不知道
I don't know.
先是比利  现在朱莉也死了
First Billy, now Julie?
听着
Look.
比利和朱莉的死的确糟糕
It totally sucks that Billy and Julie died.
但这只是讨厌的巧合  不是什么诅咒
But it's just a crappy coincidence, not a curse.
如果我们不做些什么  我担心...
If we don't do something, I'm worried --
黛莉拉  别说了
Delilah, stop.
我说真的
I'm serious.
你最好闭紧你的嘴
You better keep your mouth shut
不然你要担心的事可比诅咒严重得多了
or you're gonna have a lot more than a curse to worry about.
(来自"小可爱"的聊天请求)
(我好无聊  想来一发吗)
当然
Hells yeah.
(当然  快过来  STD)
(我们会用套套的吧  哈哈)
"你在哪"
"Where are you?"
(别担心  我身子很干净  不过希望我们能干点肮脏的事  你在哪)
是你吗
Was that you?
不是
Nah.
真会捉弄人
What a tease.
喂
Hello?
现在是什么时候
What time is it?!
是谁
Who the hell is this?!
声音关小点  老兄  我还要学习呢
Lower the tunes, brah! Trying to study!
你还好吧
Are you okay?
不太好
Not really.
有什么发现
What do you got?
被强噪音震死的
Death by decibel.
什么
What?
凯尔的大脑被他的音箱震烂了
Kyle's brains were jellied by his speakers.
对了  还有  他音响上的钟表
Oh, and get this. The, uh -- the clock on his stereo
停在8点10分上
stopped at 8:10.
-810  -对
- 810? - Yeah.
又是
Again?
我们知道是你去送的花
Look, we know you're the one leaving the flowers.
为什么不跟我们说实话
So, why don't you just tell us
安德鲁·西尔弗车祸那天晚上究竟发生了什么
what happened the night of Andrew Silver's accident?
黛莉拉  求你了
Delilah, please.
这是5天里的第三起命案了
This is the third death in five days.
天知道下一个会轮到谁
Who knows who's gonna be next?
是我
I am.
那起车祸
The car accident...
其实不是意外
wasn't exactly an accident.
(新年  新室友  新机遇  上帝保佑)
伙计  我刚刚转发了你的推文
Dude, I just retweeted your tweet.
我刚给你点赞了
Dude, I just favorited yours.
看这里
Okay, here.
自拍一张
Oh, selfie.
我的天
O-m-g.
我就像个老太婆  看着有25了
I am such a hag! I look like I'm 25.
所以才要用滤镜来美颜嘛
Oh, that's what filters are for.
删了删了
Delete.
看这个  等等
Check this. Wait.
-好了  等等  -好了  再来
- Okay, wait. - Here. Again. Come on.
我发给你了  看
I'm sending it to you, dude. Here.
再拍一张
Let's do one more so I can --
天啊  比利  快报警
Oh, my god. Billy, call 911.
快报警啊
Call 9-- call 911.
不  不
No. No!
(唐斯大道810号)
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
我得在警察到之前快逃
I'm getting out of here before the cops come.
我们刚刚害死了那个人
We -- we just killed that guy.
不行  不许报警
No. Hey, you're not calling the cops!
我已经酒驾过一次
'Cause I already have a D.U.I.,
如果被发现我的驾照是吊销的
and if they find out I'm driving on a suspended license,
我会进监狱的
I'm going to jail.
不行  比利  这样不对
Come on, Billy. This isn't right.
帮帮我  伙计们
Help me out here, guys.
别管了  小黛
It's not our problem, Dee.
什么
What?!
会有人报警的
Someone else will call the cops.
谁都不许说  听到了吗
Not a word. You hear me?
我不该听他们的话的
I shouldn't have let them talk me out of it.
不该那样
It was wrong.
现在我们遭报应了
And now we're being punished.
真的  怎么可能
Seriously, what are the chances
一周之内  四个人死了三个
that three out of the four of us die in one week?
不可能是巧合
It can't be a coincidence.
不是巧合  是鬼
It's not a coincidence. It's a ghost.
安德鲁·西尔弗的怨鬼
It's the vengeful spirit of Andrew Silver.
鬼
A ghost?
对  鬼是存在的
Yeah. They're real.
没错  我们就是干这个的
Yeah, it's sort of what we do.
你们是捉鬼的
So, you're, like...ghostbusters?
嗯  现在的当务之急
Sure. First things first, though.
是我们去捉鬼的时候
You need to stay inside this salt circle
你得待在这个盐圈内
while we take care of him, okay?
你们怎么搞定他
How do you take care of him?
你们知道怎么搞定他吧
Please tell me you know how to take care of him.
鬼一般附在某处或某件东西上
Usually a ghost is tied to a place or an object.
只要处理掉这个东西  鬼也就消失了
You get rid of the object, you get rid of the ghost.
但安德鲁的情况
But with Andrew, it's, uh...
比较特殊
it's different.
他附在什么东西上了
What's he tied to?
我们还在找
We're working on it.
只要我们能查明他是如何移动的
But if we can figure out how he's traveling,
就能阻止他
we can figure out how to stop him.
要知道  情况可能比较复杂
You know, this might be a shocker situation.
报纸上说他是死于撞击
The paper said that he died from a collision,
但黛莉拉说他是触电而死
but Delilah says that he died from electrocution.
也许他就是那么移动的
So maybe that's how he's surfing.
利用电线穿梭
He's using the power lines as a conduit.
电脑和音响的事可以说得通
I mean, that would make sense with the computer and stereo kills,
但卡车事故不行
but not the pickup.
开车靠的是油
I mean, the truck runs on gas.
那就得接着查了
All right, it's got to be something else, then.
好吧  我再去事故现场看看
All right, I'll go back to the accident site, check it out.
-你在这儿陪她  -好
- Stay here with her. - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
累了吗
You getting tired?
没有  习惯了
No. I'm used to it.
经常熬夜学习
I stay up all night studying.
其实是为了免得做噩梦
Mostly to avoid the nightmares.
我妈看我成绩好高兴坏了  但我却...
My mom's thrilled with my GPA, but I'm just...
很痛苦
miserable.
我每天都在想安德鲁
I think about Andrew all the time.
我都不认识他
And I've never even met the guy.
执迷于一个不认识的陌生人真是疯了
It's pretty crazy to obsess about someone you've never met.
也不算疯
It's not that crazy.
我明白那种感受
The truth is, I can relate.
真的吗
Really?
我犯过的错数都数不清了
I have made more mistakes than I can count.
它们让我日夜不得安宁
Ones that haunt me day and night.
那你是怎么应对的
So...how do you deal?
借酒消愁
Whiskey.
拒绝承认
Denial.
我尽力弥补过错  拨乱反正
I do my best to make things right,
无论那可能意味着什么
whatever that may be.
对于你  也许意味着...
For you, maybe it's...
也许意味着坦白
Maybe it's coming clean.
想办法寻求原谅
You know, finding a way to ask for forgiveness.
但不是破费去买花祭奠
But not breaking the bank at your local florist.
我是说...真正的原谅
I mean...real forgiveness.
这种事你不能一直瞒着
You can't just bury stuff like this.
你得去面对它
You got to deal with it.
有什么发现
Hey. What do you got?
迪恩  安德鲁不是通过电线移动的
Dean, Andrew's not using power lines to move.
他用的是无线网络
He's using wi-fi.
再说一遍
Come again?
电死安德鲁的电线
The -- the wires that electrocuted Andrew,
直接连到了无线网络塔上
they -- they feed directly into a wi-fi tower
就在马路对面
right across the street.
连鬼魂都会上网了
So, even ghosts are online?
看来是的
Apparently.
这就能解释那起卡车杀人案了
I mean, it would explain the truck kill.
比利的手机当时一定也连着当地的无线网络
Billy's cell must have been using the local wi-fi signal,
于是  安德鲁的鬼魂一定是连上了崔妮
so, uh, Andrew's ghost must have just hopped on to Trini,
那个...导航应用
that -- that -- that NAV app.
然后朱莉是被电脑杀死的
And then Julie's death by computer,
凯尔是被连着无线音箱的立体声音响杀死的
Kyle's death by stereo with the wireless speakers.
这就说得通了  迪恩
I mean, it makes sense, Dean.
我们人类也只不过是一堆电脉冲  是吧
We're all just a bunch of electrical impulses, right?
所以  安德鲁死的时候
So, whenever Andrew died,
他的脉冲一定是传到了另一股电流上
his impulses just transferred to another current.
你得把黛莉拉弄去个安全的地方
You got to get Delilah somewhere safe.
把姐妹会所有无线路由都关了
Turn off all the routers in that sorority.
好的  没问题  萨姆
Oh, yeah. Sure, Sammy.
我们会把网络"杀"了的
We'll just kill the internet.
等等  我们真能做到吗
Wait, can we?
不行  其实不太行
Uh, no. No, not really.
好吧  那我们
All right, so, then how the hell
要怎么对付"天才除草人"呢
are we gonna deal with the Lawnmower Man?
我有主意了
You know what? I have an idea.
照我说的做  保护好自己
Do what I said. Stay safe.
我等会儿打给你
I'll call you back.
你知道路由器在哪里吗
You know where the routers are?
不知道
I have no idea.
那能起作用吗
Is that gonna work?
-值得一试  -不
- Worth a try. - No!
你得把所有连上无线网的设备都关掉
Need you to turn off everything that's connected to wi-fi.
很抱歉打扰你  西尔弗太太
Uh, I'm so sorry to bother you, Mrs. Silver,
但有个急事真的需要你帮忙
But I have an emergency and I really need your help.
也许听起来会很奇怪
Now, this is gonna sound strange.
是关于我丈夫  是不是
It's my husband, isn't it?
进来吧
Come in.
-来吧  我们走  -我们要去哪里
- Come on. Let's go. - Where are we going?
去个没有无线网络的地方
Someplace that doesn't have a wi-fi signal.
地下室
The basement.
下面信号很差
The reception sucks down there.
好  走  走  快走
All right, go, go, go.
走走走  快跑
Go, go, go, go. Run.
跑
Run.
盐不是没什么用吗
I thought the salt didn't work.
因为之前有无线网络
Because of the wi-fi.
这底下没信号
There's no signal down here.
没电脑  没平板
There's no computers. There's no tablets.
没手机  所以安德鲁没法突破进来
There's no cellphones, so Andrew can't bypass it.
至少我觉得他不能
At least, I don't think he can.
就在事故发生不久后
It wasn't too long after the accident
安德鲁开始联系我
that Andrew started contacting me.
怎么联系
Contacting you how?
在网上
Online.
起初  我以为只是个玩笑
At first, I thought it was just a joke,
有人在跟伤心的寡妇开残忍的玩笑
that someone was playing a cruel prank on a grieving widow.
但是安德鲁知道一些事
But Andrew knew things,
一些只有我和他知道的事
things that only he and I would know --
我俩之间的笑话  我们警报器的密码
Inside jokes, the code to our alarm,
知道我痴迷Lifetime电视台的电影
my obsession with Lifetime movies.
那时我才知道我丈夫回来了
It was then that I knew I had my husband back,
虽然只是在网上
Even if it was just online.
你从来没想过问问他  他是什么吗
Did you never think to ask him what he was?
拜托  探员
Come on, agent.
我读过书  也看过电影
I've read the books. I've seen the movies.
我知道他是鬼魂之类的  但是...
I knew he was a ghost or something, but...
我不在乎
I didn't care.
他是我丈夫
He was my husband.
而且...这样很好
And...it was great.
甚至挺浪漫
Romantic, even.
他会给我发甜蜜信息
He'd send me love notes.
我们会整晚不睡觉  追忆过去
We'd stay up all night reminiscing.
但是后来  他开始变得怪异
But then he started acting strange.
怎么个怪异法
What do you mean, strange?
我也说不清楚
I don't know.
他会忽然消失  毫无音讯
He'd just disappear, radio silence.
然后又忽然出现  开始给我发邮件
And then out of nowhere, he'd start e-mailing again.
但是他变了  变得很专注
But he was different, focused.
专注于什么
He was focused on what?
复仇
Revenge.
当大学生接二连三地死去
When the kids at the college started dying,
我就觉得是安德鲁干的
I thought it might be Andrew.
但我能怎么办
But what was I supposed to do?
去告诉警察  跟他们说是我的鬼丈夫
Call the cops and tell them the ghost of my dead husband
在报复大学生吗
was picking off co-eds?
但主要是因为
But mostly...
我不想去面对现实
...I just didn't want to face the truth.
因为我知道  他是为了复仇而归来
Because I knew it was revenge that brought him back,
如果我阻止他
and if I tried to stop him
他可能就不会回来了
that he might go away.
我不愿意再次失去他
And I didn't want to lose my husband again.
保持冷静  好吗
Just try to stay calm, all right?
什么声音
What was that?
不知道
I don't know.
求你别杀我  我们不是故意的
Please don't kill me. We didn't mean to hurt you.
是场意外  我发誓
It was an accident, I swear.
如果能重新来过
If I could do it over again,
我会做出正确的选择
I would have done the right thing.
快走
Let's go.
-去哪  -门那边
- Where? - The door.
锁上了
It's locked.
安德鲁  听我说
Andrew, listen to me.
你生气是应该的
You have every right to be pissed.
但相信我
But take it from me...
杀的人越多  你就会变得越疯狂
...the more you kill, the crazier you'll get.
鲜血会助长怒火
The blood fuels the rage.
所以你有两个选择
So, it looks like to me you've got two choices.
继续杀人
You can keep killing
变成自己都不认识的怪物
and become something that you won't recognize
或者放下一切
or you can move on
这是你获得安宁的唯一途径
'cause that is the only thing that is gonna give you peace.
选择权在你  伙计
So, it's up to you, man.
痛苦还是安宁
Pain or peace.
安德鲁
Andrew?
我是柯丽
It's Corey.
求你听我说
Please listen to me.
你得停下
You have to stop this.
复仇  是空洞的
Revenge -- it's hollow.
毫无意义
And it's pointless.
你回不来了
It won't bring you back.
我早该跟你说的
I should have said this earlier...
但我无法释怀
but I couldn't let go.
现在是时候了
But it's time...
我要放手了
for me to let go
你也得一样
and for you to do the same.
求你了
Please.
求求你了
I'm begging you.
就算是为了我
Do this for me.
为了我们
Do it for us.
再见
Goodbye.
(唐斯大道810号)
你确定要这么做吗
You sure you want to do this?
是的
Yeah.
我早该这么做了
I should have done this a long time ago.
进来吧
Come in.
看来选择安宁的不止安德鲁一个
Looks like Andrew wasn't the only one who chose peace.
是啊  看来是这样
Yeah. Looks like.
我也该和他学学
I think I'm gonna follow his lead, too.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的安宁就是帮助他人
My peace is helping people.
查案子
Working cases.
我就想干这个
That's all I want to do.
这跟血印有关吗
Is this about the mark?
我不想再纠结于治愈方法了  萨姆
I'm done trying to find a cure, Sammy.
迪恩  小卡就快成功了
Dean, Cass is so close.
成功什么
To what?
我们都不知道是否真有治疗办法
We don't even know if there is a cure.
目前为止  我们一无所获
So far, we've got nothing.
记录者图书馆里毫无记录
We have found nothing at the men of letters library,
梅塔特隆可能知道什么  可能不知道
Metatron may or may not know something,
小卡也只是可能能从该隐那儿查到什么
and maybe Cass is onto something with Cain --
-可能  -对  可能
- Maybe. - Yeah, maybe.
世事无把握  迪恩  但那又如何
Nothing is guaranteed, Dean. So what?
我们不能就因此缴械
We can't just stop fighting.
我们可以
Yes, we can.
所以就这样了
So, this is it.
你要放弃了
Y-you're just gonna -- you're just gonna give up.
不不  我不是要放弃
No. No, I'm not just gonna give up.
我很感激你们所做的一切  真的
I appreciate the effort, okay? I do.
但答案不在外面
But the answer is not out there.
答案就是我
It's with me.
这事得由我来决定
I need to be the one calling the shots here, okay?
我不能每天早上怀着虚妄的希望醒来
I can't keep waking up every morning with this false hope.
我得清楚自己的处境
I got to know where I stand.
不然我会发疯的
Otherwise, I'm gonna lose my freakin' mind.
所以在力竭之前  我会继续抗争
So, I'm gonna fight it till I can't fight it anymore.
尘埃落定时
And when all is said and done...
我会虽败犹荣
I'll go down swinging.